sportsnewscaster.com 2010-11-22

# Privacy :: Sports Newscaster

This statement discloses the privacy practices for Sportsnewscaster.com

At Sports Newscaster we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit Sports Newscaster on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. We do however keep track of information that is not personally identifiable, such as the domains from which people visit us. This information is analyzed for trends and statistical purposes. There are also times when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.

If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example â€” it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this personal information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us.

It is our goal to protect and secure the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is secure, accurate, current and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner.

**What information do we gather?**  
Information on Sports Newscaster are gathered in two ways: (1) indirectly (for example, through our site’s technology); and (2) directly (for example, when you provide information on various pages like subscribing via e-mail for updates on WWNN.co.uk).

One example of information we collect indirectly is through our Internet access logs. When you access WWNN.co.uk, your Internet address is automatically collected and is placed in our Internet access logs.

We collect information directly from you in a number of ways, some of which we describe in this Privacy Statement. One way is through the use of cookies. Cookies are small files of information which save and retrieve information about your visit to WWNN.co.ukâ€”for example, how you entered our site, how you navigated through the site, and what information was of interest to you. The cookies we use identify you merely as a number. (If you are uncomfortable regarding cookies use, please keep in mind you can disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in preferences or options menu in your browser.)

We also collect information when you voluntarily submit it to us. Throughout our site, we provide the opportunity to register for an event or conference, order a white paper, or participate in an online survey. When we collect this type of information, we will notify you as to why we are asking for information and how this information will be used. It is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it.

**How do we use this information?**  
We analyze it to determine what is most effective about our site, to help us identify ways to improve it, and eventually, to determine how we can tailor Sports Newscaster to make it more effective. We may also use data for other purposes, which we would describe to you at the point we collect the information.

**What about sensitive personal data?**  
We do not generally seek to collect sensitive personal data through this site. If we do seek to collect such data, we will ask you to consent to our proposed uses of the data. We may also collect some sensitive personal data incidentally. By providing us with unsolicited sensitive personal data, you consent to our using the data subject to applicable law as described in this Privacy Statement. The references to “sensitive personal data” are to the various categories of personal data identified by European and other data privacy laws as requiring special treatment, including in some circumstances the need to obtain explicit consent. These categories comprise personal identity numbers, personal data about personality and private life, racial or ethnic origin, nationality, political opinions, membership of political parties or movements, religious, philosophical or other similar beliefs, membership of a trade union or profession or trade association, physical or mental health, genetic code, addictions, sexual life, property matters or criminal record (including information about suspected criminal activities).

**Do we give you access to our information?**  
You are entitled to know whether we hold information about you and, if we do, to have access to that information and require it to be corrected if it is inaccurate. You can do this by sending us an e-mail.

**What about data security?**  
We take appropriate steps to maintain the security of your data on WWNN.co.uk. You should understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended.

That’s it in a nutshell. The short of it is we are interested in maintaining your privacy and creating a valuable resource for you to use. If you have any questions now or during your visit, please [contact us](http://www.sportsnewscaster.com/contact/).
